Heiwa Fansubs Presents:
"Great Detective Conan"
"Challenge to Kudo Shin'ichi"
Whoever you are, stop it already!
It keeps getting bigger.
What're we gonna do, Shin'ichi?!
Ala? Let's go.
Hey... what's this date?
Probably... that case.
"Ramen Revolutionary, Noguchi Hyogoro"
"Naguchi Family Eldest Daughter
Noguchi Yuri"
What are you doing here?!
The mistress's child shouldn't be butting in!
Listen!
"Noguchi Family 2nd Daughter - Noguchi Miki"
I may be his mistress's child...
...but I'm the one Father loved most!
You're calling him Father?!
You're just a good-for-nothing!
At any rate, your only objective is his money!
Huh?! You bitch pig!
Get out right now!
*"Noguchi Family Butler - Kamoshita Ryosuke"
Stop this! Yuri-ojyosama!
"Suzuki Sonoko"
Miki-san, calm down!
Let go!
Thank you for waiting.
What was Sonoko doing at
the funeral of the Ramen King?
Her Dad and him were close friends,
and their families socialized.
Ah... Rich people are all connected
to one another.
Ah, here's my chance.
If you don't want it, I'll take it.
Eh... Ah?!
You're terrible!
I was saving that for last.
Revenge!
Whaa, you...
I was saving that for last!
Geez...
Ah!
"Incoming call
Suzuki Sonoko's Home"
It's from Sonoko.
Hello...
No way?! Sonoko has?!
What's the matter with Sonoko?
She's been kidnapped!
Eh?
"Hyogoro Ramen Headquarters"
"Legendary Meat Soup!"
What do you mean by
Sonoko's been kidnapped?
I got a phone call at the crematorium...
I don't know if it was a man or a woman.
The voice had been processed.
"I've kidnapped your older sister,
Noguchi Yuri."
"If you want her returned to you,
have 10 billion in diamonds prepared."
Diamonds...?
"If you don't abide by these demands,
your sister will lose her life."
"We don't have just your sister."
"Wait... what do you mean?!"
Then the phone got cut off.
After the funeral...
...both my sister and Sonoko-chan seem to have
left the temple and been together since then.
So it looks as if Sonoko-chan
was kidnapped as well.
Sonoko...
Sonoko, pick up!
It's no good... It's been turned off.
Yuri-san's car was found in
the temple's parking lot.
"MPD Investigation Unit One
Takagi Wataru"
So your sister and Sonoko-san were probably
kidnapped together at the temple.
Has there been a ransom demand
made to Sonoko's family?
Not at present.
But... that's weird, isn't it?
Because even Sonoko's family
is incredibly rich.
Is it that the criminal doesn't know that...
...and their only target is to take money
from the Noguchi family...?
Yuri?
Yuri?!
Yuri!
Miki-ojyosama.
I have brought the diamonds.
- Thank you. Put them there.
- Yes.
This is the first time I've seen
so many diamonds.
"MPD Investigation Unit One
Sato Miwako"
It's because the Ramen King was
known for his diamond collection, huh?
Ah... you dropped them.
This is terrible, terrible...
Thanks to my sister, these'll be squandered.
You were having a big fight with her on TV...
...but truth is,
you do care for your sister, don't you?
You're wrong.
If we're stingy with the ransom money
and my sister is killed...
...that would damage
the Noguchi family name, wouldn't it?
Is that right...
It would be best to put
the diamonds all in one place.
Kamoshita.
Bring me my attache case.
Certainly.
It's OK.
If you would please.
Hello?
"Are the diamonds ready?"
Yes, they're prepared.
Please let me hear Yuri-oneesama's voice.
"It would be better for you to pray for
her safety than hear her voice."
"Attach the diamonds to the rooftop
ad-balloon and send it skyward."
Skyward?
"At 3 o'clock."
"Once we've checked the contents, we'll notify
you of the whereabouts of the two people."
Please give it to me!
How's Sonoko?
Are you with Sonoko?!
Hello?! Hello?!
The trace failed!
Shin'ichi...
Give it to me!
There's only 10 minutes left.
Let's hurry.
How are they going to check
the contents from the sky?
Fool.
They're going to check it now.
Kyaa!
Are you okay?
I just fell down for a moment.
I'll carry that.
Yes.
If you would please.
Just the sort of feel you'd expect from
10 billion yen worth of diamonds.
Let's go.
Everything's fine over here.
Same here.
How will the criminal snatch away
the diamonds from such a place?
Will a helicopter come?
Eh?!
It's 3.
No one's coming to get it.
Should we bring it down?
Let's wait a little longer.
We'll wait a little longer.
I wonder why the criminal isn't appearing?
Did they notice the police activity?
We were taking the latest precautions,
so that can't be so.
It's been an hour now...
Hello?
"We've got the diamonds."
What's that?!
Was that the criminal?
They said, "We've got the diamonds."
Bring down the balloon!
The diamonds... are gone!
The diamonds disappeared?!
Miki-ojyosama...
"As promised, the hostages will be returned."
"Go to the bench at Beika Central Park."
Beika Central Park?
Why...?
"Beika Central Park"
It said Beika Central Park bench,
but which bench?!
At any rate, let's split up and look for it.
- Look at that one, please.
- Yes! Certainly!
I'm sorry, may I look here?
Excuse us a moment!
I'm sorry.
- Ran-chan, over there, please.
- Ah, yes!
Excuse me! Excuse me a moment...
I'm sorry.
Damn!
Where is it?
"Go to the underground depot."
Underground depot?
There is an underground depot
at the headquarters.
It's no good! It's locked!
Sonoko!
Sonoko, are you in there?!
Here is the master key.
Ah, thank you.
Sonoko!
- Sonoko!
Sonoko, are you okay?
Where is Yuri-ojyosama?
Yuri-sama... Ojyosama!
Are you okay?
Kudo-kun...
Thank goodness.
Ojyosama! Yuri-ojyosama!
Kamoshita...
Are you injured?
I'll remove the ropes from your feet now.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes. Yes, I'm fine.
This is bad!
Miki-san, on the roof!
She's dead...
Miki...
Yuri-oneesan...
Why has Miki-san...
Right after we went to
Beika Central Park, Miki-san was...
It was the act of the kidnapper
who was lurking somewhere, wasn't it?
"This is strange..."
"The criminal got the diamonds..."
"...so why was it necessary for them
to kill Miki-san?"
Well then, please tell us what happened
when you were kidnapped.
Yes...
I was waiting for Yuri-oneesan, who said
she'd forgotten something at the temple.
But since she didn't return at all,
I went back...
"Yuri-oneesan?"
"Kyaa!"
"Yuri-oneesan!"
By that time, I was already unconscious.
I had been made to breathe in
some drug from a handkerchief, too...
Is that right...
I'm sorry.
For getting Sonoko-chan involved in this.
No...
Then, did either of you
get a look at the criminal?
I didn't get the chance to see
anything but their back.
When I came to, I was in that room.
Right before my eyes...
Yuri-oneesan had been tied up as well.
Yes.
Then the lights suddenly went out and...
The lights?
Yes...
When they came on again,
Oneesan had fallen over.
I think someone had come in
and made me breathe in the drug again.
And from then until Kamoshita woke me up,
I don't remember anything...
Sonoko.
Did the light only go out that once?
No.
There was one other time...
Just a little before you guys
came to save me...
...they went out again.
I thought so.
Eh?
I've seen it.
The one and only truth.
It's impossible for 10 billion in diamonds
to just disappear from the sky.
What's more likely is that before
they were even put up in the sky...
...they had already been substituted.
Substituted?!
When? By whom? Where?
Weren't we with the attache case
all the way up to the roof?
Everyone, please line up in turn
the way we were then.
I will stand in for Miki-san...
...and Detective Takagi and Sonoko
and Yuri-san, you stay with Ran.
If you would please.
Well then, let's run.
And, start!
Stop!
Detective Sato, can you see me from there?
I can't.
Ran, how about you?
I can't see you!
It was just for a moment,
but Miki-san had entered a blind spot here.
If there was a chance for
a substitution, this would be it.
This is it.
Huh? Where?
Miki-san...
...used this.
Ready?
Beforehand, she had put a fake case in here.
And then, when she put the real case in...
Shin'ichi...
...are you saying Miki-san
substituted the attache case?
Yeah.
At that time, Miki-san pretended to fall down
here after substituting the attache case.
"Kyaa!"
"Ah, are you okay?"
Wait!
But then the case I was carrying that time...
"I'll carry that."
"Yes."
"If you would please."
"Just the sort of feel you'd expect from
10 billion yen worth of diamonds."
If it had been
replaced with that empty case...
...it should have felt lighter.
Something that was the same weight as
the 10 billion in diamonds was put in here.
What's more, it was something
that would disappear over time.
Something that would disappear?
Most likely... dry ice.
Please recall what happened on the roof.
"Should we bring it down?"
"Let's wait a little longer."
Miki-san wanted to stop then because the dry ice in
the substituted case hadn't finished evaporating yet.
But, why would Miki do such a thing?
Because she was the criminal.
The criminal?!
This kidnapping was Miki-san's little play.
However, Miki-san was then
killed by the other criminal.
You're saying she had an accomplice?!
If true...
...then shouldn't the attache case with
the 10 billion in diamonds still be in here?
No.
The diamonds have already been collected
by the accomplice.
The one who could have done that...
There's just one person.
Who would that be?
Let's go to the underground depot.
Is there a clue here
that'll lead to the criminal?
Yeah.
You've made a lot of insinuations.
You should tell me clearly.
Who is the criminal?
The criminal is...
You.
Noguchi Yuri-san.
Me?
It was because you two didn't want anyone to
realize you would be complicit together in it...
...that you deliberately staged a
violent quarrel at that funeral, wasn't it?
What do you think you're suggesting?
That's absurd.
I was confined down here the entire time.
Sonoko-chan is my witness.
Right, Sonoko-chan?
Yes...
How are you saying I could have
taken away the diamonds and killed Miki?
There was another substitution
made in this room, too.
Substitution?
You used Sonoko in order to
create an alibi for yourself.
What do you mean?
I don't understand what you mean.
What Sonoko saw wasn't Yuri-san.
It was a mannequin.
A mannequin?
The lights in this room went out twice.
The first time was so that Yuri-san
could substitute in a mannequin.
That way, while we were up on the roof...
...Yuri-san could sneak out of this room
and collect the attache case with the diamonds.
At that point...
...yours and Miki-san's plans for the
make-believe kidnapping were complete...
Or were supposed to be.
However, you headed for the roof instead.
"Why have you come here?"
"Moreover, what was that about
Beika Central Park?"
"That's different from what we had planned."
"The real plan starts here."
"Eh?"
"Killing you... will complete the first plan."
And when the light went out the second time...
...this time it was so the mannequin
could be substituted out for Yuri-san.
You had us set off for Beika Central Park
so you could make the time you needed...
...to return to this room.
"Sonoko!"
"Sonoko! Answer me!"
The light was operated by remote control.
Kudo-san...
Everything you've said are fabrications.
And even if I did,
what evidence do you have?
Kamoshita-san is holding the evidence.
Kamoshita is?
Kamoshita-san...
...please show us what you picked up in this room
at the time we rescued Sonoko and Yuri-san.
"Are you okay?"
"Yes..."
"You're not injured?"
"I'm fine..."
I am very sorry.
I just wished for you two sisters...
I wanted to protect the Noguchi family
with all my heart...
That was from when you killed
Miki-san on the roof, wasn't it?
I think it most likely got into your pants hem
while you were killing her.
And then it fell out again in this room.
Just like the great detective
you're rumored to be.
That's right...
I'm the one who killed her.
But, the one who created that
make-believe kidnapping plan was Miki.
Rather than having our father's
large bequests be hit with inheritance taxes...
...it was she who suggested
we make up a kidnapping...
...with a fictional criminal who would steal
the 10 billion in diamonds.
Miki, from the time we were children...
...could come up with cunning schemes like that.
Father loved that in her so much.
That's why Father felt Miki
was the only one he adored.
In his will after all, he was giving her,
his mistress's child, far more than me!
So frustrating...
It was frustrating...
Frustrating, frustrating...
I was always thinking,
"Someday I'll look back in triumph over Miki."
With this...
...I could prove I was
even more cunning than she was.
Even from Heaven...
...I think Father would admit to that as well.
It was just by accident that pearl
got caught in your pants.
But, that accident...
...may have been caused by
your Father in Heaven...
...in order to make you compensate
for your crimes.
You're wrong!
It wasn't an accident!
Miki... Miki did it.
She...
Right to the very end,
she was a cunning girl.
"Diamond"
Shin'ichi?
Nothing's changed...
Somehow...
I have a bad feeling about this already.
It's still far from over.
Nothing's happening.
Kyaa!
That was... an electric shock.
An electric current?
Ow!
"The Molester is a murderer?!"
"Mystery of the Artificial Respirator
that Stopped"
"This Drama Is Fictional"